A Guide to the Directors correspondence and subject files of the Commission on Population Growth and Development, 1967-1995 (bulk 1989-1994)
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 36388], 1972-1995 (bulk 1989-1994), Extent: 11 cu. ft. (11 boxes). (Box 1-11)
  - Subject files, Environment, Proceedings for the 6th Annual Symposium on the State of the Environment and Pollution Prevention in Virginia, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, Environment, Southside Economic Development Commission, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, Environment, Virginia Environmental Endowment, Grant, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, Environment, Virginia State Park Foundation, Legislation, 1989-1995 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, Environment, Voting Summary Chart of Key Environmental Legislation from the 1991 Virginia General Assembly, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, Environment, Water Issues, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, Environment, Water Issues, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, Environment, Water Issues, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, Executive Committee, 1989-1995 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, Facts and Figures Project, 1989-1995 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, Finance, Fiscal Stress, 1989-1995 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, Finance, Long-term debt, 1989-1995 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, General, 1989-1995 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, Comprehensive Data Network Project, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, Conferences (Norfolk and Richmond), 1992-1993 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, Data Information, 1989-1995 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, Letters of support, 1989-1995 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, Mapping Applications in Virginia, Survey results, 1989-1995 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, Planning District Commission meeting, 1992 December 15 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, URISA, 1989-1995 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, Virginia Geographic Information Network, General, 1989-1995 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, Virginia Geographic Information Network, Miscellaneous, 1989-1995 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, Virginia Geographic Information Network, Proposal for legislative Action, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, Virginia Geographic Information Network, Quarterly reports, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Geographic Information Systems, Virginia Geographic Information Network, Slide show, 1993 December (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Government structure, 1989-1995 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Governor's Commission on Government Reform, Blue Ribbon Task Force, 1989-1995 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Growth Management, Development and Planning, Attitudes of Virginians Regarding Growth and Development - Survey Report, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Growth Management, Development and Planning, The Economics of Growth Management - A Background Reader, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Growth Management, Development and Planning, Future Development of the Commonwealth: Sustaining, Managing and Generating Growth, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Growth Management, Development and Planning, Governor's Commission on Virginia's Future: Toward a New Dominion, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Growth Management, Development and Planning, A Historical Overview of State and Regional Planning in Virginia, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Growth Management, Development and Planning, History of Planning in Virginia, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Growth Management, Development and Planning, Implementing State Growth Management in the U.S.: Strategies for Coordination, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Growth Management, Development and Planning, Planning in Virginia: Growth Management in Virginia, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Growth Management, Development and Planning, State Growth Management, Land Planning and Regulation Programs, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Growth Management, Development and Planning, State Growth Management Legislation, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Growth Management, Development and Planning, State Growth Management Programs, 1989-1995 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Growth Management, Development and Planning, State Role in Growth Management: Alternatives and Implications, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Historic Preservation, Financial Impact of Historic Designation, Report of the Virginia Dept. of Historic Resources on (S.D. No. 23), 1992 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Historic Preservation, Public/Private Partnerships for Encouraging Historic Preservation in the Private Sector, Report of the Va. Dept. of Historic Resources (H.D. No. 72), 1993 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Housing, Affordable Housing, 1989-1995 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Housing, Annual Report of the Virginia Housing Study Commission, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Housing, Examining the Role of State Government in Revitalizing Virginia's Central Cities, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Information Technology, Virginia Report on Planning for Information Technology Resources, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Infrastructure, 1989-1995 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Internship, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, Land Use, Findings and Recommendations on a State Posture in Land Resource Issues, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Land Use, Land: Issues and Problems, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Land Use, Land Use Law Reform Symposium, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Land Use, Land Use Policies, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Land Use, State funding for land protection, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Land Use, State Land Use Planning, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Local Government, Change in the Commonwealth: City/County Experience in Virginia During the Decade of the 1980s, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Local Government, Local planning legislation (Title 15.1), 1991 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Local Government, The Need to Review Virginia's Local Government Structure: Report of the Local Government Attorney's of Virginia, Inc., 1988 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Local Government, State Aid to Localities, 1989-1995 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Local Government, Summary of Proposals by Commission on Local Government: Structures and Relationships ("Grayson Commission"), 1989 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Local Government, Virginia Assembly on the Future of Local Government in Virginia, Final Statement, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Local Government, Virginia Assembly on the Future of Local Government in Virginia, Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Local Government, Virginia Association of Counties, Comments to the Local and State Government Infrastructure and Revenue Resources Commission, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Local Government, Virginia Association of Counties, Statement to the Commission, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Local Government, Virginia Local Government Growth Management Survey, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Lucy Expenditure, 1989-1995 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Public meeting, Original comments, 1991 October (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Past conferences, 1989-1995 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, General-P.D.C, 1989-1995 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, A.L. Philpott Southside Economic Development Commission, Report of the (H.D. No. 45), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Boundary options, 1989-1995 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Encouraging Compact Development, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Forward Southwest Virginia: Report of the Southwest Virginia Economic Development Commission, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, JLARC Public Hearing, 1994 June 28 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Map of high and low growth areas, 1989-1995 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, A Metropolitan Government for the Richmond Region?, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Northern Virginia, 1989-1995 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Planning District Commission's Regional Resources Issues, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Regional Service Delivery-Reference material, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Regionalism: Pre-1994 Information, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Regionalism: Share Decision Making- A Background Reader, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Remarks of John Jenkins, President, VAPDC to the CPGD, 1991 April 25 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Responses: Environmental Issues, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Rethinking American Regional Planning, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Review of Virginia's Regional Planning District Commissions (JLARC), 1994 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Review of Virginia's Regional Planning District Commissions, Draft (JLARC), 1994 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Review of Virginia's Regional Planning District Commissions (JLARC), 1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, "The Role of Substate Regionalism," 1994 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, State and Local Services Responsibilities-Subcommittee meeting, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Town-County Fiscal Relations: The Issue of Double Taxation (H.D. No. 81), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Virginia Association of Planning District Commissions, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, Virginia Investment in Planning: FY 90 Local and Regional, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Planning District Commissions and Regionalism, "Virginia's Planning Districts: Past Achievements and Future Prospects," 1986 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Population, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Public Education and Participation Program, Public Information Session, 1991 November 15 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Rural Development, General, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Rural Development, Governor's Rural Development Conference, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Strategic Planning, A Review of Strategic Planning Process, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Strategic Planning, State, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Strategic Planning, State, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Strategic Planning, State, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Tourism/Travel, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Transportation, Infrastructure, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Transportation, ISTEA-Surface Transportation, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Transportation, ISTEA-Mass Transit, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Transportation, Study of Transportation Trust Fund Allocation Formulae (S.D. No. 39), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Transportation, Traffic, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Transportation, Transportation Issues, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Urban/Metropolitan areas, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Virginia American Planning Association Conference, 1992 January 30 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Speeches, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Speeches, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Speeches, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, List of materials, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Arkansas, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, California, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Colorado, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Connecticut, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Delaware, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Florida, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Georgia, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Illinois, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Louisiana, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Maine, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Maryland, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Massachusetts, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Minnesota, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Nevada, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, New Hampshire, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, New Jersey, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Oklahoma, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Oregon, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Rhode Island, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, South Carolina, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Texas, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Utah, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Vermont, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Subject files, Information/Legislation on Population Growth and Development in Other States, Washington 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Clippings, General, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Clippings, General, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Clippings, General, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Clippings, General, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Clippings, General, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Clippings, General, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Clippings, General, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Clippings, About Commission, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Clippings, About Commission, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Newsletters, Growth Commission Update, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Newsletters, Growth Commission News, 1991-1994 (Box 11)
  - Newsletters, Water News, 1991-1994 (Box 11)
- Series IV: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 50419], 1991-1995, Extent: 13 cu. ft. (13 boxes). (Box 1-3)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 2)
  - Meeting files, 1991-1995 (Box 3)
  - Strategic plans, 1991-1995 (Box 4)
  - Meeting files, 1991-1995 (Box 5)
  - Meeting files, 1991-1995 (Box 6)
  - Financial records, 1991-1995 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence and Administrative files, 1991-1995 (Box 8)
  - Financial records, 1991-1995 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence and clippings, 1991-1995 (Box 10)
  - Phone logs, 1991-1995 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 12)
  - Meeting files, 1991-1995 (Box 13)